// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Which of these supported by Ruby?",
      answer: "Programming Language",
      options: [
        "Automatic Memory Management",
        "Multiple Programming Paradigms",
        "Dynamic Type System",
        " All of the Mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: " Which of the following features does the 2.0 version of ruby supports?",
      answer: "All of the Above",
      options: [
        "Security fixes",
        "Method keyword arguments",
        "New literals",
        "All of the Above"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "Ruby is?",
      answer: "scripting language",
      options: [
        "markup language",
        "procedural language",
        "stylesheet language",
        "scripting language"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "Ruby is designed by?",
      answer: " Yukihiro Matsumoto",
      options: [
        "Guido van Rossum",
        " Tim Berners-Lee",
        " Yukihiro Matsumoto",
        "Brendan Eich"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "Ruby was created in?",
      answer: "1993",
      options: [
        "1992",
        "1993",
        "1994",
        "1995"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which of the following statement is not a feature of ruby?",
      answer: "Ruby can not be connected to Database",
      options: [
        "Ruby can not be connected to Database",
        " Ruby is interpreted programming language",
        " Ruby can be embedded into Hypertext Markup Language (HTML)",
        "Ruby can be used to write Common Gateway Interface (CGI) scripts"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Which of the languages syntax matches with the Rubyâ€™s syntax?",
      answer: "Perl",
      options: [
        "Java",
        "Jquery",
        "Perl",
        "PHP"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: " What is the extension used for saving the ruby file?",
      answer: ".rb extension",
      options: [
        " .rrb extension",
        ".rb extension",
        " .ruby extension",
        "All of the above"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "What is the sequence of ruby strings?",
      answer: "8-bit bytes",
      options: [
        "8-bit bytes",
        "32-bit bytes",
        "64-bit bytes",
        "16-bit bytes"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "What does the notation \b stands for?",
      answer: "backspace",
      options: [
        "space",
        "newline",
        "escape",
        "backspace"
      ]
    },
  ];